unomatch.com 2017-06-30

# PRIVACY POLICY - Unomatch Shop

Unomatchshop values our customers and respects their privacy. We collect information about you through our website in an effort to improve your shopping experience and to communicate with you about our products, services, contests and promotions.

This privacy policy describes the personal information we collect about you, why we collect it, how we use it, and when we share it with third parties. Our privacy policy also describes the choices you can make about how we collect and use your information. If our information practices change, we will post an updated policy on our website. If we change the policy in a material way, we will provide appropriate notice to you. You may exercise your choices about how we collect and use your information consistent with this policy at any time.

If you have any questions about our privacy policy, please contact us at [customerservice@unomatchshop.com](mailto:customerservice@unomatchshop.com)

#### What kind of information does Unomatchshop collect?

We may collect personal information from you, such as your name, email address, postal address, phone number, credit card number, gender, birthday, personal interests, etc., when you visit our website to place an order online or by phone, make an in-store purchase, save your information with us online, contact us with a question or concern, or participate in a contest, promotion, or survey. We maintain a record of your product interests and the purchases you make online or by phone.

#### How does Unomatchshop use my information?

We may use your personal information in the following ways:

  * To process and fulfill your order, including to send you emails to confirm your order status and shipment
  * To communicate with you and to send you information by email, postal mail, telephone, text message, or other means about our products, services, contests, and promotions, unless you have directed us not to contact you with promotional communications
  * To administer and fulfill our contests and other promotions
  * To help us learn more about your shopping preferences
  * To help us address problems with and improve our site design, products and services
  * To enhance your shopping experience
  * To analyze trends and statistics
  * To protect the security or integrity of our websites and our business
  * To contact you if necessary

#### How does Unomatchshop use cookies?

Our websites use “cookies,” which are small data files that are stored on your computer when you visit a website. Cookies enable you to shop on our websites and may be used in a variety of ways to enhance or personalize your online browsing and shopping experience.

For example, we may use cookies to enable you to use certain website features, remember the items in your shopping bag, store your preferences, recognize you when you return to our website, track your orders, and monitor and maintain information about your use of our websites.

You can set your browser not to accept cookies or to notify you when you are sent a cookie, giving you the opportunity to decide whether or not to accept it. If you do not accept cookies, however, you will not be able to access your account information or make purchases on our websites.

#### How does Unomatch use pixel tags?

We use “pixel tags” (also called “web beacons” or “clear gifs”), which are tiny graphic images, on our websites and in our emails. Pixel tags help us analyze our customers’ online behavior and measure the effectiveness of our websites and our advertising. We work with service providers that help us track, collect, and analyze this information.

Pixel tags on our sites may be used to collect information about your visit, including the pages you view, the features you use, the links you click, and other actions you take in connection with the sites. This information may include your computer’s internet protocol (IP) address, your browser type, your operating system, date and time information, and other technical information about your computer. We may also track certain information about the identity of the website you visited immediately before coming to our site. We do not otherwise track any information about your use of other websites.

Pixel tags and cookies in our emails may be used to track your interactions with those messages, such as when you receive, open, or click a link in an email message from us.

We also work with third-party companies that use tracking technologies to serve advertisements on our behalf across the Internet. These companies may collect information about your visits to our websites and your interaction with our advertising and other communications.

We may combine the information we collect through cookies and pixel tags with other information we have collected from you. This information may be used to improve our websites, to personalize your online experience, to tailor our communications with you, to determine the effectiveness of our advertising, and for other internal business purposes.

#### How do I know my personal information is secure?

We do our best to provide you with a safe and convenient shopping experience. We have in place certain physical, electronic, contractual, and managerial safeguards to protect the security and privacy of your personal information.

When you enter your personal information on our websites, we use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology to protect your information as it is transmitted to us. To make sure you are accessing our secure server before you submit personal financial information, look at the lower left-hand corner of your browser. If you see an unbroken key or a closed lock (depending upon your browser), then SSL is active. To double-check for security, look at the URL or Location line of your browser. If you have accessed a secure server, the first characters of the address in that line should change from “http” to “https.”

If for any reason you cannot access the secure server, or if you’re not quite comfortable shopping online at any of our websites, please feel free to place your order with us by telephone at the number listed in the section entitled, “How do I contact you?”, below.

#### What is “phishing”?

“Phishing” is a scam designed to steal your personal information. If you receive an email that looks like it is from us asking you for your personal information, do not respond. We will never request your password, user name, credit card information or other personal information through email.

#### What about links to other websites?

For your convenience and information, our websites may contain links to other sites, which may have privacy policies that differ from our own. We are not responsible for the content or practices of any linked site. We recommend that you review the privacy policy of any site that you access through our sites.

#### Business Transactions

Unomatchshop may acquire other businesses, and another company may acquire Unomatchshop or substantially all of its assets such as through a merger, consolidation, acquisition, or asset purchase. If that occurs, the information we collect may be one of the assets examined or transferred as part of the transaction. We will not transfer the information we have collected unless the acquirer of all or substantially all of unomatchshop assets agrees to provide the same or substantially similar privacy protections as those established by this privacy policy. In the event Unomatchshop is involved in a bankruptcy proceeding, the information collected by Unomatchshop may be sold in such bankruptcy proceeding (without any requirement of a consumer privacy ombudsman) so long as the acquirer of all or substantially all of Unomathcshop assets agrees to be bound by the same or substantially similar privacy protections as those established by this privacy policy.

#### How do I contact you?

We welcome your input on our privacy policy. If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at [customerservice@unomatchshop.com](mailto:customerservice@unomatchshop.com).

Unomatchshop  
ATTN: Privacy  
13-35 B, Sperber Road, Fair Lawn,  
New Jersey – 07410, U.S.A.
